East auxränkc
.ca
All I know what I'm supposed to do?
Take your hand,
take your hand,
and take your hand away.
Let's start with the new world.
Look, look, look!
We've been waiting for a few years.
We've been waiting for a long time.
Don't
forget
We'll fight together!
We'll fight
together!
Thank you.
Damn!
That is the biggest sea
king I've ever seen!
Why is it flipping out?
It's scary!
It's dead!
Something killed it!
You gotta be joking!
I didn't get a look at what happened!
I don't think I like this place!
Is that a man? Hey! Who are you?
What a doozy.
It's you!
The Dark King Silver's relay!
What?
Oh, it's been a while.
I remember meeting you at Sabaody.
It's Gold Rogers' first mate
right here in the flesh.
So, funny story.
Things got kind of rocky in the storm.
My ship sank, so I had no
choice but to swim here.
What?
But they never have storms
in this part of the sea.
That's why they call it the Calm Belt.
But then that must mean...
He crashed in safe waters and swam
through that bit of sea kings?
How is that supposed to work?
I have a pretty good breaststroke. Right.
He says it like it's no big deal.
So you killed that giant
thing with your bare hands?
I have actual bare hands,
and I couldn't do that.
Forgive me, Dark King.
What are you even sorry for?
Sorry!
Let me be frank.
Something tells me Luffy's on
this island, is that correct?
Have you heard the news?
The princess and some others just
left to deliver food to Luffy.
They're so lucky.
I want to make those cheeks of his
stretch and stretch and stretch.
I heard they'll invite him
over once all his wounds heal.
It should be any day now.
We should hold a feast again.
It's a shame he's hurt, but
I'm glad he came back so soon.
Well, since he's here again, maybe
I'll make him another pair of clothes.
Without all the frills.
How shameful it is for newlyweds
to be separated like this.
What a tragic heroine I've become.
Sweetie, don't say that.
You know, we're always together in spirit.
Of course, dear.
No matter how far apart the world may keep
us, we are bound by a thread of passion.
Oh, Luffy.
You always know just what to say.
My heart is aflame with affection.
I can feel the desire
building up inside me.
You are hopeless.
How foolish.
I've told you any man
may remember your name,
but that doesn't mean that you're married.
Oh Then what is marriage?
What else is there to do?
That is a difficult question to answer
You're too weak to travel to Sabo
Odi especially with that wound.
I'll make it work.
I got to see my friends as soon as
possible They'll be expecting me.
I promised them I'd be there.
Well nevertheless
Now that's odd.
The submarine is gone.
Surely they didn't depart.
Oh, hello there, Luffy.
It's Rayleigh, the old guy.
Straightforward as ever, I see.
Why are you here?
I was about to use my Viva card to go to
Sabaody since my friend
should be waiting there.
So did you see them? I haven't.
Actually, it seems they
haven't made it there yet.
As for my Viva card, I ended
up handing it off to Chaka.
It's rather nice.
No one can find me, and I
can go wherever I please.
Dark King Rayleigh, I don't believe this.
Is it really you?
Hmm, you must be that former warlord.
Something wrong?
I didn't expect to come
face-to-face with a living legend.
Huh, I suppose you'd like your hat back.
Oh, yeah, thanks.
My head just doesn't
feel right without it.
There, that's a lot better.
Have you seen a group of pirates
or a submarine around here?
If you're talking about
Trafalgar Law, he took off.
He left a message for Luffy.
Stay in bed for two more weeks.
He saved your life, didn't he?
Now that was a raw deal!
All those women right there
and we were stuck on the shore!
Man, what a tease!
They said bears were welcome to visit!
Though, hey, don't tell us that!
I'm sorry!
Who cares!
I wonder what the dark king is up to?
Seems he's drawn to another
man with the will of D!
Well, whatever happens,
it's bound to be a storm!
No!
It can't be! Rayleigh!
Is that really you?
Oh, why, hello, Gloriosa.
It sure has been a while.
Hi, Rayleigh. How are you?
I'm lovely. Good to see you.
It's Luffy!
Could you show some manners for once?
Don't ignore the man who saved your life.
He saved your life so the three
of you know old man Rayleigh too?
Indeed.
It's a long story.
We'll spare you the details.
I'm so glad to see that you're well.
I've been awake for
days worrying about you.
You must be starving.
I've brought plenty of food.
Please eat to your heart's content.
You can't even bear to look at him.
How is this marriage of
yours supposed to work out?
Serve the man!
Give him some food and be quick about it!
No, Jinbei!
This cornucopia was not meant for you!
You may have one bite.
How generous.
I shall endeavor to curb my appetite.
Come, Luffy.
You need your strength and as
they say to eat is to live?
Well done back to the old Luffy already a
A letter from Chaka.
Thank you for bringing this, Rayleigh.
She hasn't changed.
Not one bit. Yeah.
If you were living in Sabahodi
again, it'd be just like old times.
She's doing well.
And you girls,
you three have gotten tough
over the past 13 years,
possessing a strength that is
only matched by your beauty.
Rayleigh, Granny Magellan, and Chaka.
If it weren't for you three,
we'd still be slaves to the
Celestial Dragons right now.
This troubles me.
If you found him, protecting Luffy
may be more difficult than we thought.
I know you're friends, but if
you could find Luffy so quickly,
I fear the Navy's search for him
may prove successful as well.
Then we'd all be in danger.
Oh, if it isn't Rayleigh.
It's me, Hancock.
Do you remember me? Really?
You just now noticed him?
Don't worry.
I doubt the Navy will guess
that Luffy's staying here.
First off,
the one who helped him
escape from the Sabaody
archipelago told me he sent
him off in this direction.
I work for the Revolutionary Army.
Because Straw Hat shares a connection
with Dragon, I will let his crew escape.
Oh, that's quite the twist.
So, where did he end up
sending our monkey boy?
Beats me.
I apologized for my abrupt manner earlier.
Can I speak with you for a moment?
I don't have much time.
Not as myself.
Now as for Straw Hat...
Kuma would only tell me what direction
he sent our friend Luffy flying in.
But even that info didn't
necessarily point to this island.
I spent a lot of time
puzzling over how Luffy was
able to infiltrate such
a heavily guarded prison.
It made enough sense that Luffy got there
by stowing away on a
Navy ship with Hancock.
But it still didn't add up.
Hancock is known to hate both
the world government and men.
I don't think she'd willingly
get on a government ship.
Certainly not to help a man.
Knowing that, how else would
Luffy have gotten there?
Have you considered this one?
Maybe Hancock met Monkey and had
a case of love at first sight.
If so, everything fits.
He is pretty cute, after all.
It's also a lovely way
to spite the Navy and
now she's got the perfect
opportunity to nurse.
her poor, injured lover
boy back to health.
I think you're letting your
imagination get carried away, Chaka.
Guess that's the power
of women's intuition.
That's my Chaka.
The snake princesses.
Well, see for yourself. Do
you like it? Please say yes.
It's all just for you.
Although our little theory turned out to
be true, it's still pretty ridiculous.
So the Navy won't act on it.
All right, it's time we
got down to business.
Hey, Luffy.
Earlier you said you're heading back
to Saboori to meet up with your crew.
Do you still plan on doing that?
Of course I do.
They need me.
Maybe they do, but is
that the best choice?
Think back.
Surely you remember how your
last trip to Sabahodi ended?
Everyone, start running
and look after yourselves!
We can't win this one.
We're too weak.
Get moving!
I couldn't save any of them.
What's wrong with me?
As you are right now,
do you think you would fare any better
if you were to face those enemies again?
I know, but I...
Do you want to be reunited with your
friends only to endure the same fate?
I would imagine that your answer is no.
So let me offer you some advice.
Do with it what you will.
Meanwhile, on the Bowen
Islands, on the Grand Line.
Come back here, Usoppun!
Don't try to stop me!
Usopp seems to be moving his massive body,
which has grown huge from eating
an abundant variety of food?
from the gorging forest.
Some might call it running.
Usoppun! It's impossible!
No, it's not.
I'll keep trying till I get it.
I can do it this time!
There you are!
Get out of my way, you big oaf!
Special attack!
Oh, no! Usoppun!
Why won't you heed my warnings? Damn it!
So close!
You can't do this!
Every time you try to
get off of the island,
terrifying creatures like the giant
beetle will stand in your way?
and force you back into the forest.
There's nothing to stop you from entering
the island, but then your fate is sealed!
Even if you can learn to
survive in the forest,
No one ever leaves this islandin' alive.
And don't forget, my name is Heraclesin!
Huh? Usoppun?
Where did you go?
Oh, no!
The sea creature in has just
crawled onto the Island!
Usoppun!
You're in danger!
The sweet flavors and intoxicating aromas
that emanate from the Bowen Islands?
attract a plethora of
giant insects and birds.
Even sea kings and other aquatic
animals visit from time to time.
It's your sea hippo.
Now's not the time to stop and stare.
The wonderful smells lead
them deeper onto the island.
There, they find ever
more tempting flavors.
But while it's easy to enter the island,
it's much harder to leave.
Another one!
Try my exploding star!
I'm getting out of here
no matter what it takes!
Don't you dare get on my way!
The islands are gonna move again!
Wait, do what now?
Stop in!
Grab a tree and hang on!
How often does this happen?
Every time it needs to feed!
The so-called Bowen Islands are
not at all what they appear.
The flower-shaped island is actually an
island-sized flower known
as the Stomach Berry
Oh, supper!
What has gotten into you?
Ever since the news coup brought that
paper, you've been acting like a maniac.
What did it say?
I can't be here!
I have to go!
I've wasted enough time
on this stupid island!
Luffy, he lost his brother in the war!
And now, he doesn't know where
we are or if we're alive!
Luffy wouldn't let me suffer like that!
I'm his friend!
I need to be there for him!
I'm sorry, Luffy!
We not long ago make friends.
Raccoon really leave now?
Yeah.
As soon as I read that newspaper and found
out what my friend's been going through,
I realized I couldn't
stick around any longer.
I had just met Luffy's
brother in Alabasta.
I can't believe what happened to him.
I'm worried about Luffy.
What if he needs medical attention?
He always pushes himself
way too hard. Good friend.
Anyway, it's good to see you and the
birds are getting along better now.
Understanding only happened because brave
raccoon friend risking life to do talking.
Aww.
You guys remember not to pick
fights with the humans, okay?
They're not gonna hurt you.
They just want you to let them pick
the plants that grow on that tree.
Raccoon, speaking truth, we
no fight you are taking eggs.
We not same as bad humans that stealing
your treasure and chase you away.
We're your friends!
Oh, by the way,
I was really impressed with that medicine
you guys gave me when
I got injured before.
It's great stuff.
See, I'm better already. Right.
We using special medicine recipe we
passing down over many generations.
To tell you the truth,
I wish I could stay here with you guys
and study those plants for a while.
I'm sure there's still a lot I could learn,
but the timing's kind of bad right now.
Come back soon, okay?
Not right.
You're always welcome here, Raccoon.
Really?
That makes me so happy.
After my friends and I find each other,
I'll tell them all about
this amazing place I found.
And I promise, when I can,
I'll come back and visit, okay?
Take.
Journey long.
Maybe get hungry. Oh, wow. Thanks.
See Raccoon soon.
Hey!
I love cotton candy!
So long, everybody!
Be nice to each other!
Goodbye, raccoon!
You travel soon!
Now that I've got a yummy lunch
and all the cotton candy I can eat,
I'm ready to head for the
meeting spot so I can help Luffy!
Wait!
I just realized I don't
have a pirate ship!
Woohoo! Lucky me!
Why didn't I think of
this in the first place?
I'll be there in no time flat.
You're so fast, Mr. Bird.
Hey, News Koo, I'll take one of those.
I can read this while I have my lunch.
They should have some new
info about the war by now.
What?
That's crazy!
No way.
I don't believe it.
Luffy!
What's going on?
This is Gloom Island on the Grand Line,
home to the ruins of the Monkey Kingdom.
An old castle remains
from the long-dead empire.
Despite its age, a well-known
figure has made the castle his home.
Why did Mario have to get himself killed?
You're being a pest.
Go and cry somewhere else.
How can you be so heartless
when I'm grieving?
Show some compassion, you big Moon!
Do you have anything kind to say?
Offer me a tissue!
I'm your guest!
Your manners are appalling!
I never invited you.
The two of you showed up and
started living here without asking.
Furthermore, this article
is not credible. What?
But does that mean Moria
could still be alive?
He made it out?
A good question, now you ask.
If he died, then I didn't see it.
Although, if he did escape, then I
didn't see that either, I'm afraid.
But you think he might have survived and
they're lying about it for some reason?
Honey?
Kitty!
You can't fix that with your spits!
Who even taught you that
garbage, your grandma?
Bastards.
They may be stupid, but
damn, they're strong.
At this rate, I'm never
going to make it to the sea.
Hawkeye.
It's been quite a while since you left the
castle, yet you've only made it this far.
Pity.
And the boat I offered you, it
seems it's not seaworthy now.
Shut up. It's fine.
We could just hold on to a
few planks and swim there.
I'm not one to give up
that easily, all right?
Your sentiment is admirable,
but you can't defeat them.
They're called humandrills, baboons that
develop by imitating human behavior.
Humandrills?
Had they grown up among peace-loving humans,
they would have turned out differently.
But not on this island.
Up until seven years ago, this
was the site of a great war.
When I first came here to live, the entire
island still smelled of blood and smoke.
Everywhere, dead bodies
littered the ground.
As the battles raged on,
these baboons watched the violence
between the humans unfold.
In time, they learned how to
use human weapons and armor,
becoming warriors of the forest.
Humans can defeat ordinary animals
by using weapons and intellect.
But what happens when
animals don weapons as well?
As you can see, they make formidable
opponents for an arrogant young man.
You talking about me?
Well, who else?
Now, let's leave. It's late.
that your mandrels won't
set foot near the castle.
Yeah, you got no right
telling me what to do.
I've got to make it to the sea.
Of course.
Do as you like.
I don't care if they're
forest warriors or monkeys.
I've already wasted enough
time stranded in this dump.
Meanwhile, on the floating
island of Weatheria,
the world's foremost meteorologists are
busy coping with a most unruly guest.
I'll give back what I borrowed!
Just let me out of this
stupid bubble jail!
Horridus!
Get Horridus, and he'll sort this out!
Gritty, please!
We're old and you're scary!
Who knows what kind of
trap you're plotting?
This is a place of law.
You'll be punished for your crimes.
Yes, what if we shocked
her or drowned her a bit?
Which better befits a thief?
Ugh, you guys got it all wrong.
Please, let me out, at
least give me a trial.
No way, Missy!
Oh, hello, Horidot.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Well, well, what a pickle.
Hey, young lady. Hey yourself.
Another outburst.
You just weren't made to
take it easy, were you?
But never fear.
You remember this fellow, right?
Here, I'll show you a trick.
Take your tightly tied wind knots like so.
Hurrah, snow!
I was counting on you to help me!
Get me out of here!
I'm in a rush, all right?
Are you okay?
Hard enough speak to us!
Tell us you're not dead!
Uh, yes or no.
I mean, maybe.
She hit that kind and gentle
man! What a beast! Doctor!
Someone call the doctor!
That's most curious.
So she stole an armful of weather
balls in our research notes,
which then tried to make a break for it?
See for yourself.
It's all right here.
Young lady.
I'm a pirate.
What did you expect?
What's wrong with the little theft?
Got to make a living somehow, don't I?
Simply reprehensible,
such an awful human being.
We have no villain in our midst.
Whatever shall we do?
Just let me go.
You guys don't want me here,
and I don't want to be here.
You got back everything I stole.
What does it even matter?
Would you stop flipping out for
five seconds and listen to me?
I'm in a hurry here!
This is important!
Don't get too close!
It's terribly violent!
All right, I'm listening.
Let's talk.
Though I should tell you, stealing a
balloon was both foolish and dangerous.
You need proper training to pilot one.
You could have easily died.
Read the front page.
The paper, eh?
You see that article about
the pirate named Luffy?
He's the captain of our ship. Is he?
Oh, I've seen that fellow before.
The boy's a real upstart.
Caused quite the ruckus
in Marineford, they say.
He's famous for that
Straw Hat that he wears.
Our crew has been
separated for a while now,
so he doesn't even know
if we're alive or dead.
I had no idea what he was going
through until I read that paper.
I've been taking it easy all this time,
while he was down there
fighting for his life.
He saw his brother killed
right before his eyes.
I didn't even know.
I couldn't do anything.
Now he's waiting for me.
and for the rest of the crew, I'm sure.
Luffy is strong, but
this is too much to bear.
I want to be there for him.
I want to help him.
Hey, hey, don't cry. You'll be okay.
Hurry up and let her out.
We're the real villains.
Look at us.
Oh, abducting an innocent
young girl and making her cry!
Give Harados the key!
Quickly now!
We're sorry, young lady.
Let's sort this out.
That's hot.
Where did she go?
I don't see Harados either.
Huh?
How did she move so fast?
Thanks for everything!
Bye-bye! Huh? Bye-bye?
She pretended to cry to
take Horridus hostage,
and she's stealing our stuff again, too!
The world below isn't ready for the
genius of our research! I know! I know!
Take me to the sea!
Anywhere!
I can't do it by myself! Impossible?
Make it possible!
Luffy, hang on.
Just a little bit longer.
I'm sorry every time
we've been in trouble.
You've been there to
help us just this once.
I hope we can return the favor
You've already captured me young lady,
you don't need to pretend
to cry like that anymore
Shut up!
We now return to Futureland, Baltimore,
a mechanical island where the genius, Dr.
Vegapunk, was born.
We have an intruder!
Someone's broken into Dr.
Vegapunk's lab!
What should we do?
Damn it!
Apprehend them, but
don't use any firearms!
His inventions are too valuable!
We can't afford to have even one damaged!
Understand? Yes, sir!
Get back here!
Crap, it must have tightened security
after the last time I broke in.
Hold on, I get it now.
We can't shoot in here.
Wait, what do you mean the
lab is full of treasure?
Vegapunk is the head of the Navy Science
Division, so all of his works are valuable.
Priceless, Brittany.
Our country is very proud of him.
Although, I suppose it's his
mind that's the real treasure.
At any rate, he spent his youth
working in that lab, tirelessly.
Have you noticed that mountain?
A rather unnatural shape, isn't it?
I never gave it much thought, but
yeah, there's a story behind it.
It's a project Vegapunk began as a child.
It was meant to protect the
island's people from frigid weather.
He built it by transforming the animals
in the forest into a robotic workforce.
Unfortunately, it remains unfinished.
It's a sort of geothermal system
to heat up the whole island.
The world just can't keep
up with his imagination.
That's why so many of his works remain
buried here in a state of half-completion.
Sometimes, the technology or
funds he needed didn't exist.
Even though he couldn't get
rid of the cold knowing that he
cared knowing that he worked so
hard warmed our hearts at least
that story is super depressing?
you think so?
But the people here are
happy to wait for his return.
Whenever that may be.
Please respect our feelings
and stay out of that lab.
After all, it's equipped with a self-destruct
button, in case you wanted to know.
But why?
Not the button.
I mean, why did you think
I would want to know that?
Like I was going to press the dumb thing?
Either way, that sounds pretty scary.
Why don't we forget about
this whole mess and go home?
I'll make you some nice hot tea, okay?
Sorry, kiddo. No way.
I didn't come all the way out here
with no pants on just to turn around.
I'm getting that icebreaker
if it's the last thing I do.
don't get me wrong i appreciate
your hospitality but i read
the paper today and it turns
out that my captain has gone
through hell and back so bye
you guys have a nice life i know
it's tempting but no matter what
don't press that self-destruct
button would you give it a rest
already why the hell would i
want to do something like that i
can't believe the doctor cooked
up all this stuff when he was
so young because this is super
brilliant work if i've ever seen
it half of this is so advanced
it'll take another hundred
years before the world is ready
maybe i don't want to mess with
this as a fellow engineer i
gotta respect the man's work
did you hear the marines came by
and said someone broke into the
lab that's not good let's just
hope they catch him they're
probably looking to sell stuff
on the black market even a
blueprint from that place would be
worth a fortune but someone just
sneeze on one of dr vega punk's
masterpieces and you'll spend
the rest of your life in prison.
I don't care if you're a Marine.
Sir!
Sweet.
He's got a pirate mark, too?
I'll do it, you too.
So, hypothetically, if by some crazy
chance I press that button like you said.
Yeah, go on.
You wouldn't, like, hold
it against me, would you?
Of course we would!
News of this incident quickly
spread across the world.
And history would remember
it as Baltimore's nightmare.
You're truly a blessing from hell!
Thank you, Lord Satan.
It's unreal!
I never imagined that one day we'd
be able to fight back like that.
much less beat them
and put them in a cage.
The music, something about it changed us.
I've never felt so uplifted
before. He's right.
Courage and strength
welled up in our hearts.
We stood up and defended ourselves
for the first time in our lives.
Of course, we had no idea
how to use our weapons.
Ultimately, you did most of the
actual fighting by yourself.
But that's okay.
What matters is the people who
were abducted came back safely.
No, you're too modest.
I only helped a teeny bit.
Neither gods nor devils will help
those who won't fight on their own.
In times like these, it is important
to stand resolute against evil,
even if the odds seem insurmountable.
You have the courage.
You prove that today.
Such a wise god!
You've inspired us!
We'll do our best to make you proud!
Thank you very much for your teachings!
Hail Lord Satan!
I hope that repaid their kindness.
Still, I can't believe the news.
Please stay strong Luffy.
I hope you're all right.
I'll be there soon to share in your grief
If I had a heart it would be heavy
Until I can return to your side.
All I can do is play a song and
hope that it reaches you somehow
Dammit! Gah!
I can't believe they got the
devil as their bodyguard.
What an embarrassment They
should be the ones in cages with
those freakish single-jointed arms
of theirs on display Actually,
we can make a lot of money doing that.
Couldn't we?
Good idea.
We'll put their freakish
double-jointed arms on display.
They owe us, and we can certainly
make a lot of money doing that.
Wait just a minute.
That's wrong.
And it's immoral.
I'm certain that you didn't appreciate
it when they were cruel to you.
Everyone, listen to me.
Let them go?
How could we, Lord Satan?
They'll just come back
and attack us again.
No, they will not.
I'll make sure of that by
binding them to a devil.
contract heed my words well if you break
your oath with me and commit a wrongful
act against the people in this country
again I will hunt each of you down
and then I will eat your heart thank
you sir we promise you will behave we're
going straight back to our homes we'll
never come back again oh please don't hurt
us sorry but we don't believe in curses
oh also your speech was stupid and
you fell for the oldest trick in the
book if we bring back an actual walking
talking skeleton we can make a whole
ton of money wait a minute let me
go i have somewhere i need to be oh
no we have an emergency lord satan has
just been kidnapped everyone prepare
to summon another devil and fast yes
we can still summon devils with the
magical power of underwear luffy when
you feel sad just sing a song music
is meant to make you happy so sing as
you wait for me i'll try to no i will
be there until then if you can hear me